Contact

ppuckett21@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/paigepuckett (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Nursing

Acute Care

Certifications

Core Disaster Life Support

Paige Cosgrove, BSN, RN, CEN, TCRN

Registered Nurse at Grady Health System Gainesville

Summary

Registered nurse with strong knowledge and patient care skills in emergency care. Over six years of completed nursing experience involving staff nurse and charge nurse duties on a Medical Surgical unit as well as emergency/trauma nursing experience in a fast-paced level 1 trauma facility and academic teaching hospital. Breadth of knowledge in acute and continuing nursing care, healthcare issues, medication administration, critical thinking skills, and procedures. Clinical experience in a variety of settings. Works exceptionally well under pressure.

Experience

Grady Health System

8 years 11 months

Registered Nurse

February 2014 - Present (6 years 7 months)

Emergency Department

Ongoing experience and learning in the emergency department realm delivering care with a focus on acute and critical care management, triage skills, high-risk medication administration and emergency-specific tasks and nursing skills. Provides nursing care at this level 1 trauma center for medical emergencies involving acute care management, priority recognition, and delivery of care using effective communication with the interdisciplinary teams. Provides and manages goal-oriented patient care by utilizing established nursing processes and principles. Remains compliant with continuing education opportunities and department-specific requirements.

Registered Nurse

October 2011 - February 2014 (2 years 5 months)

6A Surgical/Trauma

Delivers a complete range of staff nurse duties that include careful history taking and plan of care initiation, medication and intervention delivery, ongoing

monitoring of patients and continuity of care that is ethically sensitive and age appropriate. Consistently ensures a safe environment and provides patient and family education. Active in unit and facility-wide performance improvement standards including patient satisfaction and customer service, safe practice, and use of evidence based practice. Enlarges professional development and leadership while participating in the charge nurse role. Provides assistance to co-workers in a team work driven unit. Participates in in-services and ongoing educational opportunities. Advanced Cardiac Life Support certified.

Piedmont Atlanta Hospital Registered Nurse April 2015 - May 2016 (1 year 2 months)

Delivered exceptional care in this busy metro Atlanta emergency department with a focus on safe, effective care, customer service, evidence-based approach to healthcare delivery within a teamwork driven unit. Responsibilities included triage skills, critical thinking, acute care procedures and medication administration, critical care delivery, and patient education. Compliant with all continuing education requirements.

Appalachian Nurse Practitioner Clinic Nursing Assistant/Lab Tech March 2010 - June 2011 (1 year 4 months) Dahlonega, GA

Northeast Georgia Health System Nurse Extern/Patient Care Tech May 2010 - May 2011 (1 year 1 month) Gainesville, GA

Education

University of North Georgia
BSN, Registered Nurse (2014)

North Georgia College and State University ASN, Nursing/Leadership · (2007 - 2011)